Privacy policy

We respect your privacy

We commit to ensuring the privacy of all our users at the website(Website).www.acf.international

This Privacy Policy governs all pages on the Website ( ). It doesnot apply to pages hosted by other organizations, related organizations or third partysites. The Website may be linked to the websites of such other parties but those othersites may have their own privacy policy which applies to them.

www.acf.international

Our Website may be used without entering personal information. Different rules mayapply to certain services on our Website, however, and are explained separatelybelow. We collect personal information from you (e.g. country of residence and emailaddress) in accordance with the provisions of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of theEuropean Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of naturalpersons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movementof such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation,GDPR). The provisions below serve to provide information as to the manner, extentand purpose for collecting, using and processing personal information by the provider.

Please be aware that data transfer via the internet is subject to security risks and,therefore, complete protection against third-party access to transferred data cannotbe ensured.

Сookies

Our Website makes use of so-called cookies in order to recognize repeat use of ourWebsite by the same user/internet connection subscriber. Cookies are small text filesthat your internet browser downloads and stores on your computer. They are usedto improve our Website and services. In most cases these are so-called ‘sessioncookies’ that are deleted once you leave our Website.

To an extent, however, these cookies also pass along information usedto automatically recognize you. Recognition occurs through an IP address savedto the cookies. The information thereby obtained is used to improve our services andto expedite your access to the Website.

You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on yourbrowser software accordingly. You should be aware, however, that by doing so youmay not be able to make full use of all the functions of our Website.

Server data

For technical reasons, data such as the following, which your internet browsertransmits to us or to our web space provider (so called server log files), is collected:

type and version of the browser you use;

operating system;

websites that linked you to our site (referrer URL);

websites that you visit;

date and time of your visit;

your Internet Protocol (IP) address.

This anonymous data is stored separately from any personal information you mayhave provided, thereby making it impossible to connect it to any particular person. Thedata is used for statistical purposes in order to improve our Website and services.

Purpose of registering

We offer you the opportunity to sign up for our Website. The information entered whensigning up, as shown in the registration form is collected and stored solely for useby our Website. When signing up for our Website, we also store your IP address andthe date and time you registered. This serves to protect us in the event a third partyimproperly and without your knowledge makes use of your data to sign up for our site.

None of this information is transferred to third parties except email addresses thatmay be passed on to third parties for newsletter purposes (see the NEWSLETTERsection below).

When registering, we ask you to confirm that you are familiar with the privacy policyand agree with it. By checking the corresponding box, you confirm your consent to thefact that your personal data will be processed in accordance with the privacy policyof our Website, and also confirm that you have reached the age of 16.

Personal data received for sending newsletters will be stored until the moment whenthe registration is canceled by the person who provided the data. Newsletterdistribution may be terminated. In this case, the personal data collected for thesepurposes will be destroyed.

Newsletter

Registration on the Website (when you indicate the country of residence and emailaddress) means that you consent to subscribe to our newsletter. The newsletterprovides you periodically with information about our services, events, new videos, etc.To receive our newsletter, we require a valid email address and country of residence.We will review the email address you provide for the purpose of determining whetheryou are in fact the owner of the email address provided or whether the actual ownerof said address is authorized to receive the newsletter. When subscribing to ournewsletter, we will store your IP address as well as the date and time you subscribed.This serves to protect us in the event a third party improperly and without yourknowledge makes use of your email address to subscribe to our newsletter. We willnot collect any other data. The data thereby collected is used solely for the purposeof receiving our newsletter. Nor is any of this information matched to any informationthat other components of our Website may collect. You may cancel your subscriptionto the newsletter at any time. You will find additional details in the email confirmingyour subscription as well as in each newsletter.

For the purpose of sending newsletters, personal data (email) can be transferredto a third party without further notice of the person who provided his data. In this case,only email is transmitted to the third party. The third party is not transferred otherpersonal data obtained during registration on the Website or in the process of using it.The transfer of personal data (email) to a third party is carried out in accordance withthe rules established by the GDRP.

Contacting us

On our Website we offer you the opportunity to contact us by email. In such event, information provided by the user is stored forthe purpose of facilitating communications with the user. No data is transferredto third parties. Nor is any of this information matched to any information that maybe collected by other components of our Website.

privacy@acf.international

Use of Google Analytics with anonymization

Our Website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service from Google Inc., 1600Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94 043 USA, hereinafter referredto as ‘Google’. Google Analytics employs so-called ‘cookies’, text files that are storedto your computer in order to facilitate an analysis of your use of the site.

The information generated by these cookies, such as time, place and frequencyof your visits to our site, including your IP address, is transmitted to Google’s locationin the US and stored there.

We use Google Analytics with an IP anonymization feature on our Website. In doing so,Google abbreviates and thereby anonymizes your IP address before transferringit from member states of the European Union or signatory states to the Agreementon the European Economic Area.

Google will use this information to evaluate your usage of our site, to compile reportson website activity for us, and to provide other services related to website andinternet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if thisis required by law or to the extent this data is processed by third parties on 

Google’s behalf.

Google states that it will in never associate your IP address with other data heldby Google. You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settingson your browser software accordingly. You should be aware, however, that by doingso you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our Website.

Google also offers a disabling option for the most common browsers, thus providingyou with greater control over the data which is collected and processed by Google.If you enable this option, no information regarding your website visit is transmittedto Google Analytics. However, the activation does not prevent the transmissionof information to us or to any other web analytics services we may use. For moreinformation about the disabling option provided by Google, and how to enable thisoption, visit .https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en

Use of Recaptcha

In order to protect input forms on our site, we use the ‘reCAPTCHA’ service of GoogleInc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94 043 USA, hereinafter ‘Google.’

By means of this service it can be distinguished whether the corresponding inputis of human origin or is created improperly by automated machine processing.

To our knowledge, the referrer URL, the IP address, the behaviour of the websitevisitors, information about the operating system, browser and length of stay, cookies,display instructions and scripts, user input behaviour and mouse movements in the‘reCAPTCHA’ checkbox are conveyed to ‘Google.’

Google uses the information obtained, among other things, to digitize books and otherprinted matter as well as to optimize services such as Google Street View andGoogle Maps (e.g. house number and street name recognition).

The IP address provided as part of ‘reCAPTCHA’ is not merged with other data fromGoogle unless you are logged into your Google Account at the time the ‘reCAPTCHA’plug-in is used. If you want to prevent this transmission and storage of databy ‘Google’ about you and your behaviour on our Website, you must log outof ‘Google’ before you visit our site or before using the reCAPTCHA plug-in.

The use of the ‘reCAPTCHA’ service is according to the Google Terms of Use: 

.https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/

Use of YouTube components with enhanced data protection mode

On our Website we use components (videos) of YouTube, LLC 901 Cherry Ave., 94066

San Bruno, CA, USA, a company belonging to Google Inc., Amphitheatre Parkway,

Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

To this end, we use the ‘enhanced data protection mode’ option provided by YouTube.

When you display a page that has an embedded video, a connection will be madeto the YouTube server and the content will appear on our Website viaa communication to your browser.

According to the information provided by YouTube, in ‘enhanced data protectionmode’, data is only transferred to the YouTube server, in particular which of ourWebsites you have visited, if you watch the video. If you are logged onto YouTubeat the same time, this information will be matched to your YouTube member account.You can prevent this from happening by logging out of your member account beforevisiting our Website.

Further information about data protection by YouTube is provided by Google underthe following link: 

https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/

Using PayPal as a payment method

If, while completing your donation, you decide to use PayPal as an online paymentservice, your contact details will be sent to PayPal during the order process. PayPalis a service from PayPal (Europe) S.à.rl \& Cie. SCA, 22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449

Luxembourg. PayPal assumes the function of an online payment service and trustee,and offers buyer protection services.

The personal data transmitted to PayPal usually includes your first name, last name,address, telephone number, IP address, email address, or other data requiredto process your order, such as the quantity of articles ordered, the article number,invoice amount, percentage taxes and invoice details, etc.

This information needs to be transferred to process your order using your chosenpayment method, mainly in order to confirm your identity and manage your paymentand the customer relationship.

Please note the following however: PayPal may also pass on your personal datato subcontractors or other affiliates, to the extent necessary for fulfilling thecontractual obligations arising from your order or for processing personal data in yourorder.

Depending on the payment type you pre-select in your PayPal account, which mayinclude payment by invoice or direct debit, PayPal will transfer the personal datatransferred to PayPal to credit agencies. The information transferred serves to identifyyou and to verify your creditworthiness with regard to the order you have placed.Please refer to the PayPal Privacy Policy for more information on the credit agenciesPayPal transfers data to and which data is collected, processed, stored and passedon by PayPal: https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full

Using Stripe as a payment method

For the purpose to proceed with payments we use Stripe. Stripe is a service from

Stripe, Inc, 185 Berry Street, Suite 550, San Francisco, CA 94 107, USA. Your data willbe sent to a server operated by Stripe, Inc in the United States.

You can find more information about Stripe here: 

https://stripe.com/privacy

Stripe also participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy

Shield Framework. For more information and to view the Privacy Shield policy, go here: 

https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000L1HMAA0\&status=Active

Use of Google Adwords

For purposes of promotion, our Website also employs the Google ad tool ‘Google-Adwords’. As part of this, our Website employs the analysis service ‘Conversion-Tracking’ from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94 043

USA, hereinafter referred to as ‘Google’. If you access our site by way of a Google ad,a cookie is placed on your computer. Cookies are small text files that your internetbrowser downloads and stores to your computer. These so-called ‘conversion cookies’cease to be active after 30 days and are not used to identify you personally. If youvisit certain pages of our Website while the cookie is still active, we and Google knowthat you, as user, have clicked on ads placed on Google and were redirected to oursite. Google uses the information obtained through ‘conversion cookies’ to compilestatistics for our Website. These statistics tell us the total number of users who haveclicked on our ad as well as which pages of our site were then accessed by each user.

However, neither we nor other advertisers who use ‘Google-Adwords’ receive any kindof information that can be used to personally identify users. You can prevent theinstallation of ‘conversion cookies’ by making the appropriate change to your browsersettings, for example by setting your browser so that the automatic placementof cookies is deactivated or by blocking cookies from the domain‘googleadservices.com’.

You can obtain the relevant data privacy policy from Google at the following link: 

https://services.google.com/sitestats/de.html

Information Cancellation Deletion/ /

You may contact us at no cost if you have questions relating to the collection,processing or use of your personal information, if you wish to request the correction,blocking or deletion of the same, or if you wish to cancel explicitly granted consent.Please note that you have the right to have incorrect data corrected or to havepersonal data deleted, where such claim is not barred by any legal obligationto retain this data.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights or have any questions about this policy,please contact us using the email provided during registration. Сontact us by email.privacy@acf.international

The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority

The person who provided his personal data has the right to lodge a complaint with thesupervisory authority, created in accordance with the requirements of the GDRP.
